"For how much can I rent out ..."
An apartment or villa, I guess ... "... without having to tax?"
Taxes do you have done something good, right?
You have made a profit.
So it is not wrong to tax.
An apartment must you check if you are allowed to rent out-
-Shelvation The condominium ... You can't always rent a rental right either.
But you can rent a villa or summer cottage.
Up to around 50,000-
-Can you earn tax -free per year.
For exceeding amount, you tax a small sum.
-Believe, you think.
-Right?
Also an income.
-Absolutely.
-The holiday ... or you change jobs.
Begin to keep in mind that the opportunity may exist.
And we got a boring reminder of the lack of equality.
And you can rent out or sell stuff.
And that quite a lot of money is at home that you can realize in this way.
-What are tied today, but as you can ... -bound money that just lies.
Good and educational.
- Tjing.
Do you know what I came up with?
You can borrow stuff too.
Fantastic.
Borrow or rent yourself when you are going to do something.
You don't have to own everything.